{
  "0":[
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "6257407f9da29df7b05f73e2",
    "correctAnswer": "After a girl is uprooted from her life, her emotions conflict on how best to navigate a new life.",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A slacker seeks restitution for a rug ruined by debt collectors.",
      "POWs are forced to build a railway, not knowing that allies are planning to destroy it.",
      "In a post-apocalyptic wasteland, a woman rebels against a tyrannical ruler."
    ],
    "question": "What is the plot of the movie Inside Out?",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fafc",
    "correctAnswer": "Natalie Portman",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Annette Bening",
      "Nicole Kidman",
      "Jennifer Lawrence"
    ],
    "question": "Who won the 2010 Academy Award for Best Leading Actress for playing the role of Nina Sayers/The Swan Queen in Black Swan?",
    "tags": [
      "acting",
      "film",
      "academy_awards",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95078b",
    "correctAnswer": "Gary Oldman",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "James Franco",
      "George Clooney",
      "Laurence Fishburne"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor has starred in both Harry Potter and Batman Begins?",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "acting",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "62573f419da29df7b05f7390",
    "correctAnswer": "It's a Wonderful Life",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "WALL·E",
      "Ratatouille",
      "Psycho"
    ],
    "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'An angel is sent to help a man by showing him what life would have been like if he had never existed.'",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "63a0396fc7d86251f9b65c58",
    "correctAnswer": "Scamp",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sparky",
      "Max",
      "Bolt"
    ],
    "question": "What is the name of the dog in the movie Lady and the Tramp?",
    "tags": [
      "film_and_tv",
      "disney",
      "film",
      "animals",
      "dogs"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "625fd74bdc0dd3b72da64d31",
    "correctAnswer": "2003",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "2000",
      "2006",
      "2009"
    ],
    "question": "In which year was Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl first released in the cinema?",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95070e",
    "correctAnswer": "Charlize Theron",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sandra Bæ Hovedr",
      "Kirsten Dunst",
      "Emma Thompson"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Mad Max: Fury Road and Prometheus?",
    "tags": [
      "acting",
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950404",
    "correctAnswer": "Halloween",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Nightmare on Elm Street",
      "Scream",
      "Child's Play"
    ],
    "question": "The Character Of Mike Myers Features Heavily In Which Series Of Horror Movies?",
    "tags": [
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "62573f789da29df7b05f739e",
    "correctAnswer": "The Departed",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Double Indemnity",
      "Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade",
      "Groundhog Day"
    ],
    "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'An undercover cop and a mole in the police try to identify each other while infiltrating a gang.'",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950729",
    "correctAnswer": "Kate Winslet",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kathy Bates",
      "Kirsten Dunst",
      "Sandra Bæ Hovedr"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Titanic and The Reader?",
    "tags": [
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbe8",
    "correctAnswer": "\"Exercise gives you endorphins. Endorphins make you happy. Happy people just don’t shoot their husbands. They just don’t.\"",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "\"I'm gonna make him an offer he can't refuse.\"",
      "\"I’m not drinking any f****** Merlot!\"",
      "\"Listen to them. Children of the night. What music they make.\""
    ],
    "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Legally Blonde'?",
    "tags": [
      "quotes",
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "625fd66bdc0dd3b72da64cef",
    "correctAnswer": "1980",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1965",
      "1970",
      "1975"
    ],
    "question": "In which year was Star Wars: Episode V - The Empire Strikes Back first released in the cinema?",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "cult_films",
      "star_wars",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950401",
    "correctAnswer": "Taxi Driver",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Graduate",
      "Midnight Cowboy",
      "Raging Bull"
    ],
    "question": "'You talkin to me?' is a line from which 1970's film?",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "quotes",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "62573f0b9da29df7b05f7384",
    "correctAnswer": "Inception",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Beautiful Mind",
      "The Sixth Sense",
      "A Clockwork Orange"
    ],
    "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'A thief who steals secrets through dreams must plant an idea into the mind of a C.E.O.'",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9506f9",
    "correctAnswer": "Matthew McConaughey",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ryan Reynolds",
      "Jim Carrey",
      "Hugh Jackman"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including The Wolf of Wall Street and Dallas Buyers Club?",
    "tags": [
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "624db9e8de6018633d31f6aa",
    "correctAnswer": "Daniel Craig",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Roger Moore",
      "Sean Connery",
      "Timothy Dalton"
    ],
    "question": "Who played the role of James Bond in Spectre?",
    "tags": [
      "james_bond",
      "film",
      "acting",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951a32",
    "correctAnswer": "Treehouse of Horror",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spooky Springfield",
      "The Halloween Haunt",
      "Evergreen Menace"
    ],
    "question": "What are The Simpsons Halloween specials known as?",
    "tags": [
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "625740139da29df7b05f73c2",
    "correctAnswer": "To Kill a Mockingbird",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cool Hand Luke",
      "The Elephant Man",
      "The Lion King"
    ],
    "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'A lawyer in Depression-era Alabama defends a black man against an undeserved rape charge.'",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950678",
    "correctAnswer": "Hugo Weaving",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tobey Maguire",
      "Timothy Spall",
      "Elijah Wood"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor starred in films including The Lord of the Rings and The Matrix?",
    "tags": [
      "acting",
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "625699009da29df7b05f72ab",
    "correctAnswer": "The Collector",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alexander Pierce",
      "Howard Stark",
      "Groot"
    ],
    "question": "In the Marvel Cinematic Unvierse, which character is played by Benicio Del Toro?",
    "tags": [
      "mcu",
      "film",
      "acting",
      "marvel",
      "comics",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  }
]
}